### +234 703 280 0451

# SUDEEN O. BADMUS

Frontend Developer Graphics Designer samsudeenbadmus2003@gmail.com 3, kayode street, ogba, lagos

### SUMMARY

A qualified software engineer with an excellent skill in analyzing and modifying existing

Software, as well as developing and testing end-user applications that match user needs - all using software

Programing languages like javascript, react, and frameworks like bootstrap to give a

Seamless experience on any device.

### **EDUCATION**

#### **TECH STUDIO ACADEMY**

 DIPLOMA IN WEB DEVELOPMENT (2023)

#### CHRISGATE COMPUTER COLLEGE

 DIPLOMA IN DESKTOP PUB. AND GRAPHICS DESIGN (2018)

#### IMMACULATE HEART COMP. HIGH SCH

 SENIOR SECONDARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATE(SSCE) 2015 - 2021

### **SURE FOUNDATION SCHOOL**

• FIRST SCHOOL LEAVING CERTIFICATE(FSLC) 2009 - 2015

### **SKILLS**

- Good leadership skills
- Computer literate
- Good negotiation skills
- Good interpersonal, communication And people management skills
- Focused and good attention to deails
- Dedicated to responsibility

### **HOBBIES**

- Reading books
- Watching movies
- Surfing the internet
- Meeting new people

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### **DESIGNATION I.T UNIT**

Ace Medicare Clinics | 2021 - 2022

- USER SUPPORT
- HARDWARE MAINTENANCE
- SOFTWARE MANAGEMENT
- NETWORK SUPPORT
- SYSTEM UPGRADES

### **DESIGNATION I.T UNIT**

Bigi Bottling Company | 2021 - 2022

- Router configuration
- Hardware maintenance
- System troubleshooting
- Network speedtest
- Router configuration

### Notable Achievements

- successfully implemented a ticketing system to streamline IT Support requests, resulting in faster response times and improved User satisfaction
- Collaborated with the IT team to design and deploy a new hospital-wide communication platform, enhancing interdepartmental collaboration and information sharing.

### **GitHub**

https://github.com/sudeen28

#### LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/poly-grammy-0267a82a8

### Instagram

instagram.com/chapo\_baddy?igsh=YzAwZjE1ZTI0Zg==